<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Vibhav Sinha</title>
    <link>https://vsinha.me/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Vibhav Sinha</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2019 23:28:52 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://vsinha.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ejecting React Native Jan 2019</title>
      <link>https://vsinha.me/blog/ejecting-react-native-jan-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2019 23:28:52 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vsinha.me/blog/ejecting-react-native-jan-2019/</guid>
      <description>Ejected react native getting started The experience of installing react native tells me that like every other react-native guide this write-up will be deprecated tomorrow. So, if you are reading this on any date after 20 January, 2019, good luck. Individual error message might survive and those pieces might continue being helpful to debug the eject process.
Disclaimer: Most probably things wont go as described below. There are just too many variables and too many updates and too many chances of missing something critical.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gcloud Logging ReadRequestsPerMinutePerProject</title>
      <link>https://vsinha.me/blog/gcloud-logging-readrequestsperminuteperproject/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 22:37:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vsinha.me/blog/gcloud-logging-readrequestsperminuteperproject/</guid>
      <description>The default functions of listLogEntries and listLogEntriesStream have auto paginate turned on by default. This itself is not an issue but when you have a really large set of logs, this can be difficult. A default google project has fair usage soft limitations setup on a number of API requests. Listing log entries is also restricted to about 60 requests per minute. This means that using any of the above methods will definitely result in Error about Insufficient tokens and limit reached ofReadRequestsPerMinutePerProject.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Sixth Extinction: Book Review</title>
      <link>https://vsinha.me/blog/the-sixth-extinction-book-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2017 18:03:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vsinha.me/blog/the-sixth-extinction-book-review/</guid>
      <description>Elizabeth Kolbert: A journalist at The New Yorker who has travelled in many ecological systems and collected her experiences in two books: Field Notes from a Catastrophe: Man, Nature, and Climate Change and The Sixth Extinction: An Unnatural History.
This book presents numerous facts and figures on how the sixth extinction event is ongoing. The last five extinction events were triggered by non-organic forces such as natural climate change or asteroid impacts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello Hugo</title>
      <link>https://vsinha.me/blog/hello-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2017 16:55:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vsinha.me/blog/hello-hugo/</guid>
      <description> Hello world, welcome to hugo blog
sample markdown  and some list  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>